Simona Golebiewski

simona.golebi@gmail.com

GitHub I LinkedIn I Portfolio

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Hi! Simona here. I'm a well-rounded **front developer** who's compiled a host of backend development experience. My main focus has always been problem solving user needs. But as I've learned new technologies and interacted with team members with diverse skill sets, I've also had several opportunities to explore and understand how integration processes work on the backend.

In addition, numerous partner and client-facing interactions have helped me master all the pieces of the development puzzle—from needs assessment to technical development to product delivery.

My technical skills include, but are not limited to, the following:

| JavaScript | - Angular | ∙Jira/Scrum |
|--------------------------|--------------------|---------------|
| Lightning Web Components | ▶Git/GitHub | ► HTML |
| ►Vue.js | ►CSS/SASS/LESS/BEM | ∙Sketch |

►AngularJS►iQuery►Firebase Authentication►Bootstrap

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior UI Developer I GroupWork

Aug 2021-Present

Mentor and train with expertise in communicating with cross-functional teams, to drive the development of project requirements.

- Lead and advise teammates to plan, design and implement best practices using the Salesforce Industries platform
- Formulate strategic plans for component development
- Suggest architectural improvements and design solutions to optimize software development
- Professional understanding of OmniStudio tools used to create dynamic customer interactions and developing user interface applications

Experience Consultant / UI Developer I Salesforce

Aug 2020-Jan 2021

Continue performing UI development duties post-acquisition in Salesforce's health insurance vertical. Adapt to parent company's mission and company culture.

- Take leadership role in fleshing out project scope and advising Accenture team on best practices using the Salesforce platform
- Craft dynamic customer interactions with OmniScripts to improve the user experience
- Integrate business forms with customer data by using DataRaptors
- Configure and customize templates that display data in a user-friendly manner with UI templates (AngularJS and JavaScript)
- Combine, transform, and process data quickly through integration procedures
- Meet BCBSM's client expectations by delivering a full-scope product within defined deadlines

Work independently & collaborate with the Accenture team to develop efficient processes for a large healthcare insurance client.

- Collaborate with Accenture team to develop processes for BCBSM's small group quoting and enrollment, renewal, and group wide changes
- Master Vlocity UI framework to maximize productivity, including gaining proprietary certifications (Vlocity Certified Platform Developer and Vlocity Insurance Product Modeling)
- Build proof-of-concept for key client (Priority Health) within tight two-week timeline to convince them
 of Vlocity's capabilities (client chose Vlocity for their next project)
- Liaise with Humana team to identify needs and configure front & backend elements accordingly
- Transform paper forms for adding dental providers to Humana's insurance network into easy-to-read online forms in the provider portal using Vlocity platform tools

Front End Developer | Grid, LLC

Oct 2017-Feb 2019

Build & improve responsive layouts using SASS/LESS and BEM methodologies, ensuring cross-browser consistency. Work autonomously & collaborate with an agile team to make concepts a reality.

Transition Fiat Chrysler Automobiles' Service Library from desktop to mobile (details here):

- Ensure 10K+ employees have a consistent user experience on mobile as on desktop
- Maintain awareness of lesser screen real estate by prioritizing & displaying essential info
- Use JavaScript and jQuery to ensure layout changes align with app's dynamic nature
- Perform rigorous testing across phone types and browsers to maximize compatibility

Other projects: *Hiring Remotely*, a responsive Vue web app to find remote jobs (search & filter).

EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

JavaScript Developer Bootcamp—Grand Circus

Detroit, Michigan I Oct 2016-Dec 2016

Experience a structured approach to self-learning I had already started months prior, in addition to mentoring & support, JavaScript fundamentals, informed testing, and peer learning opportunities.

Associate Degree in Applied Science—Nursing

Macomb Community College I 2015